Hey, that's...
Oh, it's Manami's boyfriend.
Well, he's been making
passes at her, at any rate.
Huh? Masaya?
But...
is this really me..?
If Toru can fool around
with Chiaki...
then I can have my fun, too!
Please, stop!
Who's making my body
move like this?
sTOoPM!
Manami and Nami
Sprite
I'm Toru Takamura.
I'm a college sophomore
and | have to stay...
with my relatives in Tokyo,
the Sakumotos.
By the way, the Sakumoto's
only daughter, Manami...
has a split personality!
Alll know is that it only
happens when | call her, "Nami".
And today she's disappeared
into town again.
I don't know what to
do with you!
You could've at least called
to say you'd be late...
because it rained,
or something!
You're not a child, after all!
I'm so embarrassed that you've
even got Toru covering for you!
I'm sorry.
Yes?
I'm really sorry about what
happened today, Toru.
Not at all. It was the least
| could do.
Manami's coming down with a
fever, so she's taken some medicine.
But could you tell me
if something happens?
Sure, no problem.
Thanks a lot.
I'll check her out right away!
Nami! Nami!
You awake?
What's all the racket?
What do you want?
What do you mean?
You worried me.
| wonder.
What were you doing
on such a rainy night?
And also, what did you mean
before by, "I'm disappearing"?
Actually...
Masaya asked me out
a while ago.
WHAAAT?
Toru, is something wrong?
No, sorry!
I, uh... just remembered
I've got some homework.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You've been so busy looking
after Manami today.
Would you like a late-night
shack?
No, I'm fine! It won't take
me long!
That scared me.
You're the one who scared me!
Look who's talking!
Yeah, well | went in, but
Ileft part way through.
N-No...
What's the matter, Manami?
Just be quiet.
Don't tell me you chickened out.
Especially considering how into
it you were, up until now.
The timing's just wrong.
You shouldn't play around
with a man's heart like that.
Let go of me!
There's no point in fighting,
Manami!
I'm not Manami!
When | left, | suddenly heard
Manami's voice...
even though she's always
asleep when I'm awake.
Don't scare the crap
out of me!
| was positive that you'd...
Your imagination's
running wild, stupid.
Don't go getting a stiffie.
Owww!
8o, Manami's your kind
of woman, huh?
Huh? What do you mean?
Now that | think of it, Manami
had a thing for you, too.
You're a lucky guy.
How could you do that?
That's your punishment for
fooling around with Chiaki.
You're wrong!
Chiaki just hates Manami.
That's the only reason she
made a pass at me.
If Manami wakes up while
I'm out...
I'll disappear, since I'm
not the main personality.
Would you cry for me,
if | disappeared?
Stop thinking such crazy things.
I'd do something.
You'd be putting yourself out.
If | disappeared, you'd be able
to go steady with Manami.
But | like Manami AND you,
Nami!
Huh?
I'll try summoning Manami
and explaining it to her.
If | can find some way
that you won't disappear...
How would you summon her?
Well...
I've just gotta go back to the
point where Manami disappeared.
You mean you wanna do
something naughty?
D-Don't be ridiculous!
I'm serious, here!
I'll believe you!
| can't stop myself...
Sorry!
Be gentle there.
How'd it go?
Perfect! | came!
That's not what | meant!
I meant, did you manage
to contact Manami?
Not yet.
What now?
We can't go any further...
Don't you wanna do it?
What?
Are you sure?
Yeabh, if it's with you.
Aha! At last, the day's come
when I'll lose my virginity!
If you don't mind using
my body, that is.
Thanks to you, | had
a great orgasm.
Now I'm gonna return
the favor.
HOOORAAAYM
H-Hang on a second!
Stop using my body like this!
Is that you, Manami?
Can you hear me?
Yeah, | can.
Please, just try to listen calmly.
I'm a second personality
that lives inside you.
Understand?
Yeah, I've kind of felt you
were there.
| want you to try and accept
the fact that | exist.
Don't make me disappear.
I've come to your rescue before,
when you were in trouble.
Do you remember?
Vaguely.
Just as | can't exist
without you...
I think I'm vital to you.
Please try to understand.
But...!
You won't go any further
with him?
Because... 'm uh...
still a virgin.
Soam|
And anyway, you like
Toru, right?
Yeah, | do...
But I'm not ready for
anything like that yet.
Right, but you didn't come
out when Toru touched me!
That's because you were
so determined!
Uh, any chance you contacted
Manami...?
Man, you're a pain!
Just pipe down, would you?
Beg your pardon...
I'm just a big screw-up,
anyway.
Okay, I'll change places with you
right now.
But in exchange, make sure
you love Toru back.
What?
Admit it, you felt it just as
much as | did, right?
You have to do it back to him,
otherwise it's so one-sided.
| was so happy when
Toru said...
I'm a dif ferent personality
from you.
But he says he cares for me
as much as you.
He said he likes me.
As much as you.
If it'll make Toru happy...
then I'm prepared to do
anything for him.
Hey, you!
How come you're sulking
in bed?
I'm crawling in!
| like you, Toru!
Let's keep fooling around!
Really?
But tonight, don't go putting
this thing inside Manami.
What?
Then we won't even
be fooling around!
But if you break my
you-know-what...
then poor Manami won't
be a virgin anymore.
Well, I guess | can't do it
unless she gives the thumbs up.
You don't know about it,
but she has given the okay!
But I'm upset, so |
won't tell you!
Man, your personality and
Manami's are like water and oil.
How did you end up coming out
of Manami in the first place?
No way!
| don't believe it!
Are you being serious?
If you haven't figured it out,
then I'll tell you.
It was you that created me,
you know.
Huh?
Come on, what's that
supposed to mean?
Nami, | can't stop...
That's okay.
Just let it all flow into
my mouth.
There's so much...
It keeps on coming!
Unreal!
Crap! How did | end up
causing all this?
My body feels better...
but things sure aren't
clear in my head.
Good morning, Toru.
Finish up your homework?
Homework...?
Oh, | managed...
Breakfast won't be much
longer now.
Hey, where's Manami?
She left quite a while ago,
out for a walk.
M-Manami?
Oh, Toru.
Can I sit with you?
Mm-hm.
Hey, um...
Did you hear about the other
person inside you?
Yeah.
I think I'd already realized it.
So it wasn't a big surprise.
There were times when
my memory blacked out.
Sorry about last night.
| just had to summon you.
No, that's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Anyway, if you hadn't
summoned me, ...
Manami...
Without my knowing it,
this other person inside me...
seems to be growing
stronger and stronger.
I mean, if | completely
disappeared altogether-...
what would happen to me?
Um, | probably can't phrase
this very well...
But you have your own
good points.
Like your kindness, and your
deep sense of discretion.
So you'd never disappear.
Toru...
And the other personality
has its own good points, too.
But even though you
don't seeiit...
| think the charms of both
personalities are yours.
| like both sides of you,
Manami.
So let's just calm down
and see how things pan out.
I'll keep my eye on things so
it doesn't get you in trouble.
Mm-hm.
I've gotta be careful not to
summon Nami for a while.
Hey, hey!
Here.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Manami and Nami
Sprite
Hey, Manami!
There's a big sale at Pario
today, wanna go?
No thanks, not today.
Gee, Manami didn't seem
very cheery today, did she?
No, but hasn't she always
been that way?
Yeah, | guess.
What in the world's gonna
happen to me?
Manami had made up
her mind to accept Nami...
but at college she became
more and more withdrawn.
Manami says she's not going
to college today.
Toru, did something happen
to her at college?
Well, I'm in the class
next door.
| wouldn't know.
Yeah, | suppose.
Can't tell her she's worried
about her double personality.
Sakumoto's become areal
babe lately, huh?
Yeah, she's gotten so bright!
She used to be so glum before!
| knew it!
My other personality, Nami,
is much more charming!
What?
Manami's taking today off, too?
Is it a cold?
Yeah, and it's a real bugger
to get over, too.
Oh, Sakumoto's taking
today off, as well?
That's the third day in a row.
Man, this is a problem.
It was you that created me,
you know.
| created you?
But how?
Manami seems to have changed?
Well, I guess it happened around
the time Toru transferred here.
Hey, Toru!
My stomach's killing me!
Take me to the sick room.
Why don't you tell the person
in charge in your own class?
Hey!!
Are you trying to let a woman
die before your eyes?
Uh... ouch!
Hey, the nurse isn't here.
Oh, well.
Here's the stomach medicine.
I hear your dad's a doctor.
Yeah, that's right.
Then | bet when you were a kid,
you wanted to play doctor a lot.
Yeah, | guess.
In exchange for the medicine,
I'll play adult doctor with you.
Wait-what about your sore
stomach?
Forget about that!
Owww!
Manami's not at college
today, right?
What're you doing?
Hey, hey!
I'll be the doctor, and
you be the patient!
Stop, you idiot!
Don't be embarrassed
around the doctor!
No, Toru!
I'm embarrassed!
Are you being serious?
It was you that created me,
you know.
| don't believe it!
It was you that created me.
Are you being serious?
It was you...
If you haven't figured it out...
It was you that created me.
NOW | REMEMBER"!
Let's play doctor and
also transformer!
Transformer?
Manami, you become Nami,
a different person.
Nami?
Yeah, and Nami's really
strong, and she's never shy!
Okay, Nami.
Lie on your side, and pull
down your panties.
Uh-huh.
Toru! Let's play doctor!
Huh?
That's funny. It's not
like my Daddy's!
Ow, that hurts!
You're acting weird today,
Manami!
What're you talking about?
When we're playing,
I'm Nami, not Manami!
You should know that!
| did that all the time since
| was a kid"!
Um, Toru...?
Nami had been dormant
for over ten years...
but now she's come to
life again!
And she came out when she
heard me calling her!
Uh, are you okay?
Chiaki, I'm skipping classes,
S0 see you.
Huh?
Hey, wait a second...
What's with that Toru?
Well at least now | know
where Nami came from!
Manami I've figured it out!
-'ve got it.
-Huh?
Manami, do you remember
coming to my place in Sendai...
and playing doctor with me,
when we were small?
No, not at all.
Oh, | guess Nami would
be the one who'd remember.
Anyway, that's when Nami
was first created.
So if we can go back to where
we left of f in Sendai...
you'll return to your original
state, and Nami will...
Nami might disappear.
So let's go to Sendai!
Let's not sit here thinking
about it. Let's just do it!
| wonder if her mom really
trusts me that much.
She had no problems with
the idea of going to Sendai.
Guess she's worried about Manami,
a top student, being so withdrawn.
| told Manami that Nami
would disappear.
But actually, | hope neither
of you disappear, Nami.
| can vaguely remember the
roof and posts of this house...
But...
it seems familiar.
Oh, my!
You're all grown up!
Honey, it's Manami,
from Tokyo!
This is a get-well gift
from my father.
Oh, my!
Thanks so much!
What are you saying, Mom?
Looks like me!
Not you, too, Manami!
Manami, your cooking
was delicious!
Thanks very much!
Now you take care, dear!
Dad, | have a day of f tomorrow.
So I'll take aunty back
on my way home.
Oh, okay.
Good-night.
Aren't you cold, Manami?
No, I'm fine.
Oh, right.
Nami, the other personality
inside me...
was born under these stars.
You're not tired yet,
are you, Manami?
Come over to my room.
Uh-huh.
Nami! Nami!
Nami?
Yeah.
Nami, I'm about to try
and make you disappear.
But actually, | don't
want to do it.
I'm probably being
hypocritical...
but could you try
and help out...
so that you can both
return together?
Sure, that's okay.
Just do as you like.
I'm turning back into
Manami now.
Huh?|...
Oh, are you awake, Manami?
Boy, | must've been tired.
| fell asleep at some point.
Here it is.
Remember this?
Your red stethoscope!
Yeah, the old one my dad
gave me.
Remember playing doctor
with this?
You're the one who used
a felt pen to color it red.
What? | did?
| remember this red color,
but...
It does seem like Nami has
the strongest memories.
Which means, | guess...
-Anyway, let's start.
-Start what?
What do you mean?
Playing doctor, of course!
Come off it, Toru!
You're kidding!
Manami! I'm not joking around!
This is the way to cure
your split personality!
When we played doctor as kids
Nami's personality was born...
so that you wouldn't
be embarrassed.
So this time you've gotta
try it yourself.
Then things will probably
turn out differently, right?
That was the whole point
of coming here!
Mm-hm.
Now that that's settled,
let's start!
Get real-what's with
that outfit?
This is more realistic, right?
You're hilarious, Toru!
Saying, "let's play doctor”, and
looking so serious about it!
No, you can't call me Toru!
It's "doctor™
Do it just like when we
were kids, and be serious!
Otherwise, this whole thing
is pointless!
Got it?
Yeah...
Well, uh, take off your top.
And your bra, too.
| think I'm gonna end up
with a split personality!!
Doctor...
I've taken them off.
Calm down... calm down...
I've seen Nami like this
quite a few times.
But to think that Manami
would show me her boobs!
It feels like a whole
new experience!
Good, that's fine.
Next, take of f your bottoms
and get up on the bed.
What?
No..!
This is just too embarrassing!
Let's stop, Toru!
I'm not Toru!
I'm the doctor!
Listen, Manami.
We're doing this so that you
can overcome your shyness.
Those shy feelings that
make you want to back out...
or be rescued. They'll
summon your other personality.
So you've got to get over
those feelings...
otherwise you'll never
return to your true self.
Understand?
Mm-hm.
Then let me take a look
at your stomach.
Yes, Doctor.
Does this hurt here?
No.
How about here?
Or here?
Okay then, down here?
What, does this hurt?
No, it doesn't hurt.
It's a little bit stiff.
I'd better take a closer look.
Okay, now first...
What?
You MUST do what
the doctor says!
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
lam! I'm so totally
embarrassed!
Oh, | forgot to tell you.
Pull down your panties,
as well.
No way! No way!
| don't want to!
Manami!
This is your one chance
to turn back to normal!
Then you pull down my
panties, Doctor.
Who, me?
Yes!
Are you serious?
| can't! My hands won't
stop shaking!
Don't run... you mustn't
run away!
But still...!
But... but...
Please! That's enough
isn't it, Toru?
No! Don't spread me
open like that!
No! No!
It feels like air is going
deep inside...
Like he's looking so deep
inside of me!
No!
Is that from me?
No way!
Why's that sound coming
from me?
No...
It feels so good...
I'm gonna scream...
l... I'm sorry, Manami.
| got carried away.
What happened to Nami?
She didn't disappear, did she?
Forget it, you don't need to worry.
You're pretty hot, Toru.
Nami! You're okay?
Yeah.
But how about being a little
more gentle next time?
It's really sensitive, you know.
Aha, so you didn't disappear.
But when did you two
change over?
When Manami blacked out.
But we both felt it.
Ever since Manami took
her clothes off.
So what was the point
of my whole strategy?
What's with the big act?
More than half of it was just an
amateur treatment by a pervert!
Well, shall we keep going?
Hey!
Don't you think it's too soon?
Now, you must do everything
the doctor tells you!
Nami... you...
Doctor Nami's wearing
her white lab coat...
and she won't leave any
patient out in the cold.
See how swollen it is?
I'll disinfect it with my mouth
or you won't get any sleep.
This looks like a job
for Doctor Nami!
Yes please, Doctor.
Okay, since you asked
so sincerely.
Don't worry.
I'm the woman you created,
after all.
I'll cure you any day.
Manami.
| couldn't help you at all.
Hey, don't worry about it.
Anyway, Nami's helped me
out a few times...
so | think I might just
stay this way for a while.
Manami!
When | took some time of f
from college...
| was able to talk to Nami.
She was bawling, saying
she didn't want to disappear.
| started feeling sorry for her.
| figured | didn't need to go
out of my way to get rid of her.
Nami's me, after all, right?
And | sure know the fear of
feeling that I'd disappear, too.
Manami...
I'm sure I'll be a real bother
to you again, Toru.
You won't be a bother!
It's ME who's gonna try
not to be a nuisance to you.
I'll make sure that stupid
Nami doesn't get too violent!
Well excuse me for being stupid!
No way!
This mouth sure has a way
of being cheeky!!
I didn't think you were gonna
show up!!
That's even worse!
Wait up, Nami!
I'll never do you any
naughty favors again!
Keep your voice down, idiot!
I tell you, you're gonna get
Manami in trouble!"!